[
  {
    "question": "Which two Sailor Senshi are lesbian lovers?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Sailor Moon",
    "options": ["Sailor Mercury and Sailor Mars, Sailor Uranus and Sailor Neptune, Sailor Jupiter and Sailor Venus, Sailor Pluto and Neptune"],
    "answer": "Sailor Uranus and Sailor Neptune",
    "difficulity": "Medium",
    "correct_options": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Usagi Tsukino is better known as?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Sailor Moon",
    "options": ["Sailor Jupiter, Sailor Mars, Sailor Neptune, Sailor Moon"],
    "answer": "Sailor Moon",
    "difficulity": "Easy",
    "correct_options": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which superhero team inspired Sailor Moon?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Sailor Moon",
    "options": ["Power Rangers, Avengers, Naruto, DC"],
    "answer": "Power Rangers",
    "difficulity": "Hard",
    "correct_options": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these species resembles birds?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Outlaw Star",
    "options": ["Melfina, Clair, Silgrans, Misfits"],
    "answer": "Silgrans",
    "difficulity": "Medium",
    "correct_options": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which assassin lead the Anten Seven?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Outlaw Star",
    "options": ["Hitoriga, Jukai, Iraga, Leilong"],
    "answer": "Hitoriga",
    "difficulity": "Hard",
    "correct_options": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "'Tao Magic' is the short way to say what?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Outlaw Star",
    "options": ["Dragonite, Senjutsu, Seihou, Hashi"],
    "answer": "Senjutsu",
    "difficulity": "Easy",
    "correct_options": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of guitar did Ryusuke lend to Koyuki?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Beck: Mongolian Chop Squad",
    "options": ["SG, ibanez, Fender Stratocaster, Gibson Les Paul"],
    "answer": "Gibson Les Paul",
    "difficulity": "Easy",
    "correct_options": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ryusuke owns a dog, what is his name?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Beck: Mongolian Chop Squad",
    "options": ["Beck, Doggo, Kishu, Akita"],
    "answer": "Beck",
    "difficulity": "Easy",
    "correct_options": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What postion is Saku in Beck?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Beck: Mongolian Chop Squad",
    "options": ["Singer, Guitarist, Drummer, Bassist"],
    "answer": "Drummer",
    "difficulity": "Easy",
    "correct_options": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How old is Mayuri Shiina?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Steins;Gate",
    "options": ["17 Years, 16 Years, 19 Years, 23 Years"],
    "answer": "16 Years",
    "difficulity": "Medium",
    "correct_options": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What name does Okabe call Kurisu?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Steins;Gate",
    "options": ["Christina, Kulisu, Makise, Kurisu-san"],
    "answer": "Christina",
    "difficulity": "Easy",
    "correct_options": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Steins;Gate is a collaboration work between 5pb. and who?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Steins;Gate",
    "options": ["Professor Community, Future Gadget Laboratory, 6pb, Nitro+"],
    "answer": "Nitro+",
    "difficulity": "Hard",
    "correct_options": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color of macaron did Kagari give to herself?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Black Rock Shooter",
    "options": ["Red, Green, Yellow, Pink"],
    "answer": "Yellow",
    "difficulity": "Medium",
    "correct_options": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "When did the first episode of the anime air?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Black Rock Shooter",
    "options": ["March 2012, February 2012, January 2013, August 2012"],
    "answer": "February 2012",
    "difficulity": "Hard",
    "correct_options": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What sport club did Yomi join?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Black Rock Shooter",
    "options": ["Football, Basketball, Volleyball, Baseball"],
    "answer": "Volleyball",
    "difficulity": "Easy",
    "correct_options": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the Main protaganist?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Chrno Crusade",
    "options": ["Chrono, Satella Harvenheit, Viede, Rosette Christoper"],
    "answer": "Rosette Christoper",
    "difficulity": "Easy",
    "correct_options": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "How old was Rosette when she met Chrono?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Chrno Crusade",
    "options": ["12 years old, 10 years old, 14 years old, 16 years old"],
    "answer": "12 years old",
    "difficulity": "Medium",
    "correct_options": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Chrono's brother?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "amime": "Chrno Crusade",
    "options": ["Gurio, Sister Kate Valentine, Aion, Shader"],
    "answer": "Aion",
    "difficulity": "Easy",
    "correct_options": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Layer 2?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Serial Experiments Lain",
    "options": ["Religion, Love, Girls, Boys"],
    "answer": "Girls",
    "difficulity": "Hard",
    "correct_options": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Lain's Sister?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "Serial Experiments Lain",
    "options": ["Mizuki Arisu, Yasuo Iwakura, Taro, Chisa Yomoda"],
    "answer": "Mizuki Arisu",
    "difficulity": "Easy",
    "correct_options": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Layer 7?",
    "category": "Anime",
    "anime": "serial Experiments Lain",
    "options": ["Kids, Distortion, Ego, Society"],
    "answer": "Society",
    "difficulity": "Hard",
    "correct_options": "4"
  }
]
